VoxClass — Real-Time AI Teaching Co-pilot
Lecturers can't tell who's lost. VoxClass fixes that.
Both the lecturer and student sign in simultaneously
Session created — students join with a 6-digit code or QR scan
Lecturer uploads a real APU lecture PPTX — 32 slides
LIVE: Both screens sync automatically as the lecturer navigates
Student signals CONFUSED — the lecturer sees it the moment it's tapped
"1 student confused (33%)" — confusion alert fires on the lecturer screen
Signals tab: Generate Clarifying Questions or Re-explain This Topic with AI
AI-generated questions pushed live — student sees them instantly on their screen
Student can tap "See AI Answer" or type their own response
VoxClass — built in one week for Shortcut Asia Internship Challenge 2026